你被监视着
You are being watched.
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
联系系统管理员
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
身份不明
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
身份不明
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
关键执行人
我们不
We don't.
失踪
关键执行人
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
状态：纽约警局任职
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第二季 第十四集
右边  右边
Pick right, pick right.
你妈打电话来了  小白佬  叫我送你上学呢
Your mama just called, opie, told me to take you to school.
是吗  你准备好爆米花了吗
Yeah, did you get your popcorn ready, man?
我可准备上演好戏了
'Cause I'm about to put on a show.
-成了  -不是吧
- Oh, yes! - Hell, no.
你本来能拦住
You might have blocked that
可是被你的裙子绊住了  野人
if you hadn't tripped on your skirt, bigfoot.
你小子挺有趣  算你运气
You lucky you're funny.
你说这位新号码从大学退学了
You said our latest number dropped out of college?
罗根・皮尔斯大二时离开了加州理工  没错
Logan Pierce left Caltech after his sophomore year, yes.
他另有所好
He had other aspirations.
别想上篮  别想上篮  小弱鸡闪开
No layups, no layups. Get that weak stuff out of here.
不可能  这是犯规
No way, son, that was a foul.
这里不论犯规
Ain't no fouls out here.
看来不是当职业球员去了
Guessing it wasn't to become a professional athlete.
真格儿的
Been real.
我得走了  我约了你的妞儿
I gotta jet though. I got a date with your girl.
是啊是啊  随便吧
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
来吧
Make it rain!
回见了  贱人们
Later, bitches!
这家伙到底什么人啊
Who the hell is this guy?
皮尔斯可不仅是个大学缀学生
Pierce is not just a college dropout.
他是凭借自己的天才白手起家的亿万富豪
He's a self-made billionaire with a genius IQ.
他创建了一个社交网站
Started a social networking site
名叫"友网"
called Friendczar.com
跟他的大学挚友一起创建的
with his best friend from college.
我还以为是你发明了社交网站  芬奇
Thought you invented social networking, Finch.
皮尔斯加以完善
Pierce perfected it.
他的网站有近十亿用户
His site has just shy of a billion users.
皮尔斯是"友网"的首席工程师和负责人
Pierce's chief engineer and front man for Friendczar.com,
他的长期生意搭档贾斯汀・奥美
his longtime business partner Justin Ogilvy
是资金和营销专家
is the money and marketing guru.
他们是一起创建的公司
And they started the company together?
是的
That's right.
对奥美来说  要是皮尔斯现在死了
It would certainly not be in Ogilvy's best interest
对他可没好处
to have Pierce turn up dead now.
72小时后"友网"就要上市了
They're taking Friendczar public in 72 hours.
我们得监听皮尔斯  我没法克隆他的手机
We need ears on Pierce. I couldn't clone his phone.
就算克隆了也没用
Wouldn't matter if you could.
皮尔斯一天换两部手机
Pierce changes phones twice a day
以防商业间谍
to avoid corporate espionage.
友网主办慈善拍卖会
善款将用于支持美国独立发明人
看来他今晚要出席
Looks like he's supposed to attend
一个慈善拍卖会
a charity auction tonight.
根据媒体消息
Promised the press a sound bite.
你有何计划
And your plan is?
经典黑
Classic black,
缎切口翻领  当然是定制的
satin notch lapel, bespoke, of course.
我想你应该会系吧
And I assume you know how to tie one of these?
你还在跟那个匿名线索啊
You following up on the anonymous tip?
是的
Yeah.
你真认为是警察杀了戴维森吗
You really think a cop killed Davidson?
我认为很多警察
I think a lot of cops have reason
都恨不得内务部警探去死
to want an IAB detective dead.
然后我意识到戴维森并非
Then I realized Davidson wasn't the only cop
去年失踪的唯一警察
who went missing last year.
斯蒂尔斯警探
Detective Stills.
你之前不是跟他同在51局工作吗
Didn't you two work together in the 51st?
很久以前了
Long time ago.
两名警察失踪  尸体从未被发现
Two cops go missing, their bodies never found.
这事儿不对劲
Something's not right.
-卡特  -警探
- Carter. - Detective.
我发了封邮件给你
I'm emailing you the details
内有涉及罗根・皮尔斯的若干诉讼
of several lawsuits involving Logan Pierce.
原告有暴力史的
Plaintiffs with a history of violence,
有前科的
prior convictions.
你所谓的"若干诉讼"到底有多少
What exactly did you mean by "several lawsuits"?
200个  不过我已经排好序了
200, but I've already prioritized them.
你就不用谢我了
And no, there's no need to thank me.
小熊
Bear.
来嘛
Apport.
我  感觉格格不入
I'm feeling a little out of place here.
别担心  我会陪你
Don't worry, I'll talk you
应付任何可能遇到的情况
through any difficult encounters that may arise.
芬奇  我看到皮尔斯了
Finch, I got eyes on Pierce
还有他的搭档贾斯汀・奥美
and his partner Justin Ogilvy.
十几年的挚友
Best friends for over a decade.
他们在加州理工相识
They've known each other since Caltech.
皮尔斯圈儿里的第三个人是谁
Who's the third guy in Pierce's circle?
应该是杰里米・坎贝尔
That would probably be Jeremy Campbell,
皮尔斯的律师
Pierce's lawyer.
"友网"是他事务所的唯一客户
Friendczar is his firm's only client.
我醒来发现  鼻青脸肿  处处抓痕
So I wake up, I'm bruised, I'm scratched.
我在她宿舍打电话给贾斯汀
I call Justin from her dorm room.
没错  也不打招呼  也不说早上好  上来就说
Yeah, no hello, no good morning, just,
贾斯汀  我好像被个妞儿在床上暴打了
"Justin, I think I got beat up by a girl in bed and..."
没错
I did.
我好像还挺享受的
"I think I kind of enjoyed it."
我爱死了
I loved it.
记住你叫约翰・威利
Remember that you're John Wiley,
对冲基金经理
hedge fund manager.
干嘛不用约翰・鲁尼  资产经理人
What about John Rooney, asset manager?
不不  他只是个百万富翁
No, no, he's a single-digit millionaire.
约翰・威利身价要过亿
John Wiley is valued at over 100 million.
你到底有多少钱
Exactly how much money do you have?
皮尔斯  贾斯汀  你们看上去真阔
Pierce, Justin. You're both looking rich.
本  你看上去真  熟
Ben, you are looking... mature.
我好像伤风了
I feel a cold coming on.
等等  你的啥慈善
But wait, isn't your little charity thing
不就是为了治这个么
working on a cure for that?
你说的那个是癌症
You're thinking of cancer.
本・卡盟及其夫人辛西娅
Ben and Cynthia Kamin,
他们的社交网站"连网"
whose social networking site Connectroid.com
自从"友网"开始后贬值近一半
was devalued by half when Friendczar debuted.
卡盟假装友好
Kamin's pretending to make nice.
芬奇  皮尔斯注意到我了
Finch, I think Pierce just made me.
先聊一下附带权益漏洞
Just mention the carried interest loophole.
你没事的
You'll be fine.
我之前没见你来过啊
I haven't seen you at one of these things before.
你什么来路
What's your story?
约翰・威利  对冲基金经理
John Wiley, hedge fund manager.
附带权益漏洞对你影响如何
How's that carried interest loophole treating you?
抱歉  我还以为你很有趣
I'm sorry. I thought you were interesting.
我错了
My mistake.
女士们  先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
请就座
Please take your seats
今晚的活动即将开始
for the auction portion of tonight's event.
看来我给他的第一印象不佳
I didn't make a good first impression.
那是因为我没意识到
Only because I didn't realize
我们这位顶级富豪
that we were dealing with a one percenter
会感觉其他顶级富豪乏味
who finds other one percenters tedious.
我们今晚的拍卖
We'll start the bidding tonight
从这件最令人梦寐以求的物品开始
with our most coveted item, a collection of letters
阿尔伯特・爱因斯坦的手写信
handwritten by Albert Einstein.
起价是一百万
We'll start the bidding for the letters at $1 million.
谁首先开价一百万
Who will start at $1 million for our opening bid?
这边一百万  谁出一百五十万
$1 million right here. Looking for 1.5.
有一百万了  谁出一百五十万
I've got $1 million, looking for 1.5.
后边一百五十万  谁出两百万
1.5 in the back, looking for 2.
一百五十万了  谁来两百万
1.5 looking for $2 million.
有一百五十万了  谁出两百万拍这些信
I've got 1.5. I need $2 million for these letters.
卡盟在和皮尔斯竞价
Kamin's bidding against Pierce.
两百万 谁出
$2 million, anyone?
这边两百万  谁出两百五十万
$2 million right here, looking for 2.5.
这边两百五十万  谁出三百万
$2,500,000 right here, looking for 3.
出到两百五十万了
We've got $2,500,000
我认为那些信
You know, I think these letters
价值远不止区区三百万
are worth much more than a piddly 3 mil.
你可以再加点油  是吧  卡盟
You could do better. Am I right, Kamin?
五百万
5 million.
出到五百万了  女士们先生们
We've got $5 million, ladies and gentlemen.
卡盟吃不消了
That's too rich for Kamin's blood.
还有别人吗
Anybody else?
对不住了  芬奇
I'm so sorry, Finch,
但这家伙太为所欲为了
but this guy is too used to getting his own way.
一千万
10 million.
一千万  女士们先生们
$10 million, ladies and gentlemen!
一千万一次
We've got $10 million going once.
里瑟先生  这次小额备用金可不够了
Mr. Reese, this is not petty cash.
一千万两次
We've got 10 million going twice.
成交  这位先生一千万竞标成功
Sold, right there to the gentleman for $10 million.
抱歉  下次再来吧
I'm sorry. Maybe next time.
无需道歉
No apology necessary.
我只是为慈善抬高价格
I was just driving up the price for charity.
失陪了
Excuse me.
芬奇  皮尔斯刚刚接到条短信
Finch, Pierce just got a text.
他离开了
He's on the move.
-给我进来  -遵命  女士
- Get your ass in here. - Yes, ma'am.
我还以为你伤风了
I thought you had a cold.
皮尔斯不光侵占了卡盟的生意
Pierce is not just encroaching on Kamin's business.
还侵占了人家的妻子
He's encroaching on his wife.
天啊
Oh, dear.
皮尔斯先生呢
Where is Mr. Pierce?
我知道皮尔斯和我应该
I know Pierce and I were supposed to give you
为11点新闻接受采访
a sound bite in time for the 11:00 news,
但他现在不太舒服
but he's indisposed at the moment.
我可以透露个消息
The one tip I can give you
"友站"的首次公开募股
is that the Friendczar IPO
将会打破纪录  创造历史
will break records and make history.
-谢谢  -皮尔斯在躲我们吗
- Thanks. - Is Pierce avoiding us?
你们计划出多少股
How many shares are you planning to sell?
董事会知道皮尔斯只听你的
The board knows Pierce only listens to you.
叫他自制一点
Get him to pull himself together.
给公司树点正面形象
Get this company some good press.
那是辛克莱・梅尔本
That's Sinclair Melbourne,
副总裁  "友网"董事会主席
VC and chairman of the Friendczar board.
仅此一次  辛克莱
This was a one-time slipup, Sinclair.
保证下不为例
It won't happen again.
先生  你的信
Sir, your letters.
你留着吧
You can keep 'em.
芬奇  皮尔斯刚离开拍卖会了
Finch, Pierce just left the auction,
但他的车不在
but his car's not here.
皮尔斯走了
Pierce is gone.
什么  他没有交通工具啊
What? He has no mode of transport.
是直升机吗
Is that a helicopter?
从曼哈顿的楼顶上起飞是违法的
It's against the law to take off from a rooftop in Manhattan.
芬奇  我们怎么能跟上这种不按常理出牌的人
Finch, how do we keep up with a guy who breaks all the rules?
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
翻译：somehacker  紫玉  芒果妖怪  鱼呆呆新年快乐     特效&后期：Will
时间轴：迟迟祝全家幸福健康  Jessie祝粑粑麻麻和TBBT群和人人影视新年快乐
翻译&校对&总监：阿好祝大家蛇年像里叔宅总一样甜蜜
我一直在联系你
I've been trying to get ahold of you.
我手机关了
I turned off my phone.
我在试几个新的探试算法
I'm working on a new heuristic algorithm.
哈罗德
Harold.
今天早上出事了
Something happened this morning.
据估计两次袭击
Current estimates for casualties
造成的伤亡极为惨重
from both attacks are very grave,
估计将有
estimated at about...
是架飞机吗
Was it a plane?
两架飞机
Two planes.
还有很多尸体未被发现
Countless bodies have yet to be uncovered
因为被深埋其中
because they are buried under about...
预计平民伤亡
In terms of civilian casualties...
我们创建IFT是为了改变世界
We started IFT to change the world.
我们的西装越来越光鲜
Our suits got nicer,
我们的威士忌越来越昂贵
our scotch more expensive.
我们改变了  但世界却还是一样
We changed, but the world stayed the same...
直到今天
until today.
我们不改变世界
If we don't change the world,
其他人就来改变
someone else will, so...
我们如何才能阻止这种人呢
what are we gonna do to stop the guys who did this?
芬奇  这位亿万富豪
Finch, looks like our billionaire
似乎精神崩溃了
might be having a breakdown.
皮尔斯看起来比
Pierce appears to be even more erratic
典型的亿万富豪还古怪
than your typical billionaire.
美腿啊
Nice legs.
他最有规律的事儿
The closest thing he has to a routine
就是每周去一次干洗店
is a weekly visit to a dry cleaner.
-你在哪儿  -我在上班
- Where are you? - I'm at work.
宝利呢
Where's Pauly?
他拿到了布鲁克林法律中心的全额奖学金
He got a full scholarship to the Brooklyn law center.
那你多半需要看我的票了吧
So I guess you will be needing my ticket then.
你有没有用
Did you use the, uh--
干冰清洗程序  当然有  皮尔斯先生
CO2 process, yes, of course, Mr. Pierce.
看来您没干净西装穿了
I guess you ran out of clean suits.
是啊
Yeah.
我其实比较习惯牛仔T恤
I'm actually more of a jeans and T-shirt kind of guy.
只有这一套西装
I only have one suit.
好西装就像好女人
A good suit is like the perfect woman.
一旦找到对的
Once you find the right one...
其他不过粪土
nothing else will do.
您真是超凡脱俗
How very eccentric of you.
-您的卡  -好的
- Your card.  - Course.
祝您愉快
Have a nice day.
里瑟先生  我将皮尔斯的钛卡
Mr. Reese, I switched Pierce's titanium card
换成了带窃听器的卡
for one with a listening device.
我还黑入了他的在线日程表
I also hacked his online calendar.
他要回办公室参加
He'll be heading back to the office
一堆"友网"的诉讼取证会
for a round of Friendczar depositions.
"友网"摧毁了我的生意
Friendczar destroyed my business.
毁了我的声誉
They ruined my reputation.
没有人回我的电话
No one returns my calls.
我也无法募集到任何风投资金
And I can forget raising any venture capital funds.
"友网"出手狠绝地买断
Friendczar is aggressive about purchasing
吞并刚起步的小公司
and absorbing small start-ups.
如果任何小公司的首席执行官敢跟他们宣战
And if a small CEO tries to go toe-to-toe with them,
就会面临专利侵权起诉
he gets sued for patent infringement,
无论这诉讼多荒唐
no matter how bogus the suit.
你能告诉我为什么罗根・皮尔斯
Could you tell me why Logan Pierce
都不正眼看他正在起诉的人吗
can't even look the man he's suing in the eye?
因为他睡着了
'Cause he's asleep.
你没有侵犯我们的专利  我们搞错了
You didn't violate our patents, we screwed up.
我们会帮你募集你之前损失的风投资金
We'll help you raise the venture capital funds you lost.
谢谢
Thank you.
下一个是谁
Who's next?
艾米莉・莫顿的律师来了
Emily Morton's lawyers are here.
好极了
Great.
据卡特警探所说
According to Detective Carter,
莫顿小姐将她的婚介网站卖给了"友网"
Ms. Morton sold Friendczar her matchmaking site,
金爱网
Alchementary.Com.
他们答应过会将她的网站推广到全世界
They promised her they'd launch her site worldwide,
但实际上  他们却让这个网站从此不见天日
and instead, they made sure it never saw the light of day.
我只看到了律师却没看到委托人
I see lawyers but no client.
我们的委托人因法定合理原因无法出席
Our client is unable to appear due to extenuating circumstances.
这么个小案子用不上"法定合理原因"条款
A frivolous lawsuit doesn't qualify as extenuating circumstances.
但有恐吓就可以
But intimidation does.
我们下午一点有董事会会议
Hey, we have a board meeting at 1:00.
让董事会来科尼岛见我
The board can meet me on Coney Island.
那儿有培根热狗
They have got these bacon-wrapped hot dogs.
外层酥脆  里层多汁
Crispy on the outside, juicy on the in.
这可是你们犹太人的噩梦啊
It's your basic kosher nightmare.
但你知道俗话怎么说的
But you know what they say,
"在科尼岛发生的"
"What happens on Coney Island--"
我看在科尼岛也发生不了什么事
Well, I guess nothing good really happens on Coney Island,
除了热狗
except for these dogs.
神经病
What a lunatic.
如果再联系不上莫顿女士
If we don't get ahold of Ms. Morton,
我们就只能撤销起诉了
we're gonna have to drop the lawsuit.
芬奇  艾米莉失踪了
Finch, Emily's missing,
她的律师暗示她被恐吓了
and her lawyer just implied she's being intimidated.
正好在庭审开始之前
Right before her suit goes to trial.
时机还真是巧啊
The timing is a little too perfect.
也许皮尔斯及其搭档
Maybe Pierce and his partner
跟其失踪有关
had something to do with her disappearance.
皮尔斯
Pierce?
还有两天就首次公开募股了
Two days before your company's IPO,
你给我在特里贝克区裸奔
and you're streaking across Tribeca?
告诉我  辛克莱
Tell me, Sinclair,
你的衬衫买来时就这么挺
do you buy all your shirts pre-stuffed,
还是你给硬撑起来的
or do you just fill 'em out that way?
过来
Come here.
让你的搭档按游戏规则来
Get your partner back in the game,
不然我就召集紧急董事会
or I'm gonna call an emergency board meeting.
你要能用LAMP建个靠谱儿的网站出来  梅尔本
When you build a viable web server using the LAMP stack, Sinclair,
开源免费服务器架构套件  操作简便易上手
公司就归你管
you're free to run the company.
实际上  你觉得董事会怎么选
In fact, let's put it before the board--
要你还是要我
You or me.
我看也是
That's what I thought.
吃午饭了  贱人们
Lunchtime, bitches.
芬奇  他自己公司的人
Finch, even his own company's
都吃不住皮尔斯的行为
having trouble curbing Pierce's behavior.
真高兴吾道不孤
Glad to hear we're not alone.
皮尔斯去科尼岛了
Pierce is headed to Coney Island.
我跟着他
I'm on it.
不太对
Something's not right.
皮尔斯开车通常很快
Normally Pierce drives fast,
但开得很稳
but he drives with precision.
我是罗根・皮尔斯
This is Logan Pierce.
我的车有点问题
I have a slight problem with my car.
没法减速
I can't slow down.
皮尔斯刹不住车了
Pierce's car won't decelerate.
现代车辆控制系统很容易被黑入
Most modern vehicles can be hacked into.
你靠近到十米以内
If you can get within 10 meters,
我应该能用蓝牙侵入
I should be able to infiltrate the bluetooth,
然后控制引擎
then access the engine control unit.
芬奇  他闯红灯了  我跟丢了
Finch, he blew a light. I lost him.
没关系  我得手了
No matter. I'm in.
有人黑入了电子控制单元
Someone has hacked into the car's ECU
安装了恶意程序
and installed malware,
把引擎锁定在三档50迈
locked the car in third gear at 50 miles an hour.
喂喂  有人在吗
Hello, hello? Is anybody there?
我的油门卡住了
My accelerator's stuck.
没法降档
I can't downshift.
变速器控制系统错误
3-4档变速故障
紧急故障处理中心
Communications and emergency services.
我了解您现在无法刹车
I understand that you can't decelerate.
会尽力帮您解决
I'll do my best to remedy your problem.
快点解决  福尔摩斯
Remedy faster, Sherlock.
我有点撑不住了
I'm kinda hosed right now.
里瑟先生  看得见皮尔斯吗
Mr. Reese, do you have eyes on Pierce?
看得见  再有10秒钟
Yes, he's about ten seconds out
他就要悲剧了
from a catastrophic accident.
你要是拦不下他  芬奇
You don't stop him, Finch,
那辆卡车就要拦下他了
there's a cargo truck that will.
芬奇  你救了他
Finch, you saved him.
到市区
Take me to the city.
跟都跟不上的人  我没法保护
I can't protect someone we can't keep up with.
你有何想法
Well, what do you have in mind?
换种战术
A different tactic.
皮尔斯先生  有位约翰・威利要见您
Mr. Pierce, there's a John Wiley to see you.
告诉他我很忙
Tell him I'm a busy man.
他要有意见  就叫保安出马
If he objects, have security show him out.
我会长话短说
I'll make this quick.
我有可靠消息  你现在有生命危险
I have it on good authority that your life's in danger.
通常  我只要跟着你
And normally I'd just follow you around,
悄悄帮忙就行  但是
help behind the scenes, but--
你钱太多
You've got too much money
资源也太多
and too many resources.
我可以保护你  前提是
I can protect you, but only if you
接下来48小时让我贴身跟着你
let me stick with you for the next 48 hours.
听起来很好玩
Sounds like fun.
看  我就知道你很有趣
See, I knew you were interesting.
运货的火车出发去得梅因了
The freight train just left for Des Moines.
十天后机器就能就绪了
The machine will be at the facility in ten days.
我一直在考虑你说想要
I've been thinking about you wanting
改变世界  造福人类
to make a difference, help people.
现在我们可以去做了
You know, we can do that now.
我们可以投资净水项目
We could invest in clean water initiatives,
可持续发展农业
sustainable farming.
我们造出了有史以来最强大的科技
We built the single most powerful technology known to man--
能发现需要帮助者的机器
A machine that knows when someone needs help.
你却拱手放过了
And you just gave it away.
我们有过机会  哈罗德
We had our chance, Harold.
我们造了  它拯救了生命
Well, we built it, and it saves lives.
拯救得不够多
Not enough lives.
我们谈过了  奈森
We've been over this, Nathan.
机器已经送走了
The machine is gone.
要是我们还有权限访问机器呢
What if we could still access it?
我们已经决定了不扮演上帝
We decided we weren't going to play God.
我们不会建后门
We weren't going to build a back door.
过去七年我俩决定了很多事
We decided a lot of things the last seven years.
那件事  是最令我不安的
And that one, I'm the least proud of.
我们已经做了该做的
We did what we set out to do.
现在  要么我们一起继续其他事情
Now either we move on to the next thing together,
要么算了
or we don't.
你决定
You decide.
金爱网改进了算法
Alchementary uses and advanced algorithm
能有效判断关系能否持久
to predict if the relationship will last,
不只是恋爱关系
and not just romantic relationships.
商业伙伴  友情  都可以
Business, friendships, you name it.
罗根・皮尔斯和贾斯汀・奥美
Logan Pierce and Justin Ogilvy
答应过我要发布金爱网
promised to launch Alchementary.
我一定要让他们信守诺言
I am going to make sure they keep their promise.
皮尔斯  兄弟
Hey, Pierce, buddy.
走之前提醒一下  今晚
Before you go, about tonight.
派对  纽约证交所  潜在投资者
Party. New York Stock Exchange. Potential investors.
是啊是啊  我一定提前到
Right, right. I'll be early.
记得把威利先生加到邀请名单里
And make sure there's an extra invitation for Mr. Wiley here.
这是在慈善拍卖会上竞拍赢你的家伙吧
Is this the guy who outbid you at the charity auction?
我们在考虑并购
We're considering a merger.
你觉得这样好吗
And you think that's a good idea,
跟个刚认识的人混
partnering with a guy you just met?
我觉得挺好
I think it's ideal.
我不够时间发现他的缺点
I haven't had time to learn all his flaws yet.
派对上见  贱人们
See you at the party, bitches.
里瑟先生  艾米莉・莫顿发过誓
Mr. Reese, Emily Morton vowed
要皮尔斯发布她的技术
to make Pierce launch her technology,
这技术甚至可以跟"友网"抗衡
a technology that would seriously compete with Friendczar.
我确定皮尔斯一定是受害人
Pretty sure Pierce is the victim,
而非行凶者
not the perpetrator.
已经有人对他动手了
Someone already made an attempt on his life.
懂黑客技术的人
Someone with hacking skills.
比如失踪的软件工程师
Someone like a missing software engineer.
之前那辆车毫发未损
Why get the exact same car
为什么又买辆一模一样的
when your old one didn't even have a scratch?
因为这是无与伦比的
'Cause it's unparalleled.
我不爱收藏  只要最好的
I don't collect toys, just the best of what I need.
一辆车  一块表
One car. One watch.
两百万  带月相
2 mil, charts the phase and the orbit of the moon,
精确到纳秒
tells time to the nanosecond,
还不用手动上弦
and I don't have to wind it.
两百万  我真是希望不用
For $2 million, I certainly hope not.
欢迎光临寒舍
Welcome to my humble abode.
你这叫"寒"吗
You call this humble?
纯麦威士忌  不加水  对吧
Single Malt Scotch, neat, right?
拍卖会上你就喝的这个
That's what you had at the auction.
不了  谢谢
No, thanks.
不过真令人赞叹
That's impressive though.
了解人是我的工作
Knowing people is my business.
我以为你的工作是
I thought your business was
为了首次公开募股陪投资人侃大山
schmoozing investors for your IPO.
虽然我的手表没精确到纳秒
My watch might not be able to tell time to the nanosecond,
不过你肯定迟到了
but you're late.
我有更好的事要做
I have better things to do.
芬奇  皮尔斯不去自己的派对了
Finch, Pierce is missing his own party.
正好
Just as well.
皮尔斯在公众场合更不安全
Pierce won't be safe in public now.
查下你的手机
Check your phone.
"友网"的首次公开募股即将
Friendczar's IPO is predicted
达到历史纪录
to reach record-breaking numbers.
你觉得自己会创造历史吗
Do you think you'll make history?
股票估值过高  没理由不会啊
Well, with stock this overvalued, how could we not?
私底下说  珍妮特  要我就多等个
You know, personally, Janet, I'd wait to buy
一两天  等股价下跌后再买
for at least a day or two till after the stock dips.
你懂我意思吧
You know what I mean?
董事会召开了紧急会议
The board called an emergency meeting.
皮尔斯已经不是"友网"的首席执行官了
Pierce is no longer CEO of Friendczar.
谁死了
Who died?
上帝  不是我吧
Oh, God. Don't tell me it was me.
看来董事会认为他们可以取代你
The board thinks they can do your job after all.
你出局了
You're out.
敬失业
Well, here's to unemployment.
我感觉不太对
I don't feel very good.
皮尔斯
Pierce?
Pierce.
放松  放松  放松
Sit back, sit back, sit back.
这是过敏反应
You're having a reaction.
你对什么过敏
Are you allergic to anything?
萘普生
Naproxen.
里瑟先生  怎么了
Mr. Reese, what's going on?
威士忌  被动了手脚
The scotch, it was spiked.
皮尔斯快要过敏性休克了
Pierce is going into anaphylactic shock.
-这就派救护车  -来不及了
- Sending an ambulance. - There's no time.
我得让空气进入他肺里
I need to get air into his lungs.
放松
Relax.
看着我  你会没事的
Look at me. You're going to be okay.
皮尔斯没事吧  里瑟先生
Is Pierce all right, Mr. Reese?
没事
Yes.
不过他要宿醉惨了
But he's gonna have one hell of a hangover.
你救了我
You saved me.
按中国文化
In the Chinese culture,
你要负责我一辈子
you'd be responsible for me for life.
真高兴我们都不是中国人
Glad neither one of us is Chinese then.
谁有权限进到你家
Who has access to your house?
就我一百多名挚友
Just a hundred or so of my closest friends.
我喜欢人群
I like people.
我喜欢派对
I like to party.
谁知道你对萘普生过敏
Who knows you're allergic to naproxen?
我不知道  我也是最近才过敏的
I don't know, I didn't develop the allergy till recently.
你为什么做这些
Why are you doing this?
有人安排你来的吗
Did somebody put you up to this?
是在为某些黑暗可怕的错误在赎罪吗
Is this penance for some deep, dark mistake?
听上去你颇有同感
Spoken like a man who's made his fair share.
我  我对错误不感兴趣
I-- mistakes don't interest me.
我从不回顾过去  只会继续前行
I don't look back. You keep moving.
这是唯一的存活之道
It's the only way to stay alive.
这理论颇有道理
Philosophy makes sense,
尤其是从一个父母破产的孩子嘴里说出来
coming from a kid whose parents went bankrupt.
了解人也是我的工作
Knowing people is my business too.
我父亲有一家小相机店
My dad owned a little camera shop.
他主要靠冲洗胶卷来赚钱
And, he made most of his money developing film.
他一直坚持做这行
And he insisted on staying the course,
直到有一天发现胶卷已经绝迹了
all the way until the point that film became extinct.
他想转去卖数码相机
And then he tried to sell digital cameras,
不过当时已经晚了
but by then it was too late
因为大家已经开始用手机照相了
because everyone had one in their phone.
他想都没想过会那样
It's like he didn't even see it coming.
失意失败后  我们失去了一切
When the business failed, we lost everything.
你觉得你这样下去的话
And you think if you're constantly evolving,
就不会重蹈覆辙吗
this won't happen to you?
当然会
Of course it'll happen.
但只要能接受改变的必然
But if you accept change is inevitable,
到时就不会被打垮了
it doesn't crush you when it does.
在技术时代  约翰
Every technology ages, John.
唯一不会过时的
the only thing that never gets old
就是和其他人的羁绊
is connecting with people.
那是每个人的向往
That's what everyone wants,
真正的羁绊
a real connection.
你恐怕得考虑
Well, you might wanna consider
失去上百挚友了
losing a couple hundred of your closest friends.
我觉得你今晚应该够刺激了
I think you've had enough excitement for one night.
我闭会眼
I'm gonna rest my eyes
让你也休息下
and give you a break.
我把那亿万富豪哄睡了  芬奇
I've put the billionaire to bed, Finch.
我们得见个面
We need to meet.
适宜散步的美好夜晚
Nice night for a walk.
怎么没带小熊来
Why didn't you bring Bear?
小熊不想出来
Bear didn't wanna come.
书上说如果家里气氛焦虑
I read that if there's anxiety in the home,
宠物也会跟着沮丧
it can make your pets become upset.
你有什么过大的压力吗
Have you been under any excess stress?
你是说除了被关在里克岛监狱12平米的小屋里
You mean besides being locked in an 11x13 in Rikers
和穿着炸弹背心在曼哈顿闲晃之外吗
and wearing a bomb vest around Manhattan?
没什么了
Not really.
给皮尔斯投毒的人能进入他家
Whoever poisoned Pierce had access to his home.
我们得让他搬走
We need to move him.
我也这么想
My thinking exactly.
我会让卡特警探
I'll have Detective Carter
检查酒瓶上的指纹
examine the decanter for prints.
你把那位朋友送到安全屋去
You can escort our friend to the safe house.
该叫那亿万富豪起床了
Time to wake the billionaire.
我醒了
I'm awake.
你是谁
And just who are you?
不想告诉我你是谁吗
You don't wanna tell me who you are?
没关系  我已经知道了
That's okay. I already know.
告诉我  你怎么能做出这么小的窃听器
Tell me, how did you make a bug small enough
装进这里呢
to fit inside this?
还有你的声音
Your voice too.
你黑进了我的车载电脑系统
You hacked into my car's computer
远程接入了加速和刹车系统
and you remotely accessed the accelerator and the brakes.
所以我猜你是动脑子的那个
So I guess that makes you the brains of the operation.
无意冒犯
No offense.
从你的定制西装看来
And judging by your bespoke suit,
你还是金主
you're also the bank.
而你  约翰
And there's you, John.
你搞定了我的保镖泽维
You took out my security guard Zvi.
他是前摩萨德特工  还是近身格斗高手
He's a former Mossad agent and an expert in krav maga.
那你是干什么的  约翰
So what is it, John?
前特种兵  前中情局特工
Former special ops? Ex-CIA?
至于你  超级有钱的黑客吗
And you, just a very rich hacker?
就你而言  皮尔斯先生
As far as you're concerned, Mr. Pierce,
我们并不存在
we don't exist.
这才是最令人赞叹的地方
But that's what's most impressive.
约翰  我查过你
John, I've been looking into you.
我说的不是你那对冲基金经理的掩护身份
And I'm not talking about your bogus hedge fund cover.
你和你的搭档似乎没有留下
You and your partner here don't seem
任何网络数据资料
to have a digital footprint.
所以我就问自己
So I have to ask myself,
这种信息时代怎么可能呢
how is this possible in this information age?
能如此隐姓埋名的人
People with that kind of anonymity,
拥有真正的力量
that's true power.
所以你看  我知道你们是谁
So you see, I know who you are.
我唯一不知道的是
The only thing I don't know
你们为什么做这个
is why you do what you do.
我提醒你一下  皮尔斯先生
Let me remind you, Mr. Pierce,
我们救了你两次
that we saved your life twice.
你现在是想继续插手我们的事
Now, you wanna keep on butting into our affairs?
还是想保住小命
Or do you want to live?
用不着激动嘛
No need to get testy.
我只是随便聊聊
I was just making small talk.
有什么计划
So what's the plan?
恐怕你现在谁也不能相信
I'm afraid that you can't trust anyone.
我们要带你去附近的安全屋
We've arranged to take you to a safe house nearby.
你们不希望有人找到我
You don't want anyone to find me,
却让我待在城里吗
but you're keeping me in the city?
你有更好的选择吗
You know a better place?
纽约
圣彼得堡
这到底是什么地方
Where exactly is this place?
我们飞了十个小时了
We just flew ten hours.
你就不能再多等一分钟吗
You can't wait one more minute?
怎么样
So what do you think?
你说你有安全屋
You said you had a safe house.
-是啊  -这是酒吧
- Yeah. - This is a bar.
不  这  这是个防空洞
No, this-- this is a bomb shelter
改造成的酒吧  绝对安全
made into a bar, and it is totally safe.
请坐
Sit, please.
来  来嘛
Come on. Come on.
真棒
This is good.
我们到这里来干嘛
What are we doing here?
你喜欢欧式饺子吗
Do you like pierogies?
我极度确定这里有
I have it on very good authority
全世界最好的  所以
they have the best in the world, so--
你让我飞越了半个地球
You flew me halfway across the world
就为了炸饺子
for fried dumplings?
双炸哦
Double-fried.
小熊  看
Bear, look.
犬类
抑郁
警探  我正想跟你打电话呢
Detective, you're just the person I wanna speak to.
给罗根・皮尔斯下毒的人  调查有进展了吗
Any closer to discovering who poisoned Logan Pierce?
酒瓶上有残缺的指纹
Got a partial print off the decanter,
已经放入指纹识别系统对比了
sent it through AFIS.
找到了一个匹配对象  有11处相同点
Came up with a match with 11 points in common.
这家伙的指纹没有存档
The guy's prints weren't on file
因为他是法庭相关人员
because he's an officer of the court.
最好吃慢点
Might wanna slow down.
你要是心脏病发  我可救不了你
I can't protect you from a heart attack.
你得享受生活
You know, you need to enjoy life.
谁像你这么懂得享受生活呢  皮尔斯
Who knows how to enjoy life as much as you, Pierce?
他怎么找到我们的
How did he find us?
"他"收到了皮尔斯的短信
He got a text from Pierce.
你就是喜欢让我
I think you actually take pleasure
跟你屁股后边跑啊
in making me schlep after you.
等等不行吗
These couldn't wait?
-什么  -我们说好了的
- What? - I thought we agreed.
-不找朋友  -他也是我的律师
- No friends. - Well, he's also my lawyer.
董事会把我除了名
You know, and the board forced me out.
这种情况下  他们就放弃了我的"竞业禁止"条款
And in doing so, they relinquished my non-compete clause,
这就好了  因为我正式开始
which is good, 'cause I am officially
找新工作了
looking for a new job.
里瑟先生  有件事要告诉你
Mr. Reese, something you should know.
坎贝尔的指纹出现在威士忌酒瓶上
Campbell's prints were on the decanter of scotch.
董事会让皮尔斯做了体检
The board made Pierce take a medical exam
以购买公司保险
for his corporate insurance.
文件是他的律师填的
His lawyer filed the paperwork.
你在他的酒里下了药
You spiked his alcohol.
你看了他的投保单  知道他的过敏情况
You read about his allergy on his insurance application.
你想杀他
You tried to kill him.
杰里米
Jeremy?
是真的吗
Is that true?
不  这太荒谬了
No, that's absurd.
你是我最好的客户  唯一的客户
You're my best client, my only client.
皮尔斯计划首次公开募股之后更换律师事务所
Pierce plans to switch law firms after the IPO is released.
我怎么会希望你死呢
Why would I want you dead?
也许因为你唯一的客户
Maybe because your only client
正在找新律师
is looking for a new attorney.
我有跟你说话吗
Was I talking to you?
你他妈以为你是谁啊
Who the hell do you think you are?
你最好还是把手收回去
You might wanna keep your hands to yourself.
你在威胁我吗
You threatening me?
皮尔斯  我们错过好戏了吗
Pierce, are we missing all the fun?
我坦白
Full disclosure,
我可能跟一两个人提过我们的小旅行
I might have mentioned our little trip to one or two people.
你也不能指望我满脑子生意  是吧
I mean, you can't expect me to be all business, can you?
如果你都不把自己的安全当回事
If you're not gonna take your safety seriously,
那我又何必呢
why should I?
得了  放松点  伙计
Oh, come on. Relax, dude.
来狂欢吧
Join the party!
坎贝尔已经不是威胁了  芬奇
Campbell's no longer a threat, Finch.
皮尔斯已经一堆朋友了
Pierce has got enough friends.
他不需要我们的帮助了
He doesn't need our help.
想来杯咖啡吗
Hey, you want a coffee or something?
不用了  谢谢
No, I'm good, thanks.
话说你在干什么
What you doing here, anyway?
有人让两名警察凭空消失
Somebody made two cops disappear without a trace.
你多半是不愿意
Probably not the kind of stuff
把这些摊在你桌子上吧
you wanna leave lying around your desk, huh?
我在想那个亿万富豪
Been thinking about the billionaire,
他的律师想对他下杀手
his own lawyer trying to do him in.
我为他难过
My heart breaks for him.
我很高兴有你支持我
I'm glad you got my back.
你想说什么  弗斯科
You got a point, Fusco?
卡特  有些我的事情  你应该知道
Carter, there are some things you should know about me.
-我犯过一些错  -不
- Some mistakes I've made-- - No.
我们不来这一套
We're not doing that.
不要跟我分享这些
You don't get to share that with me.
你说你改了  所以我会相信你
Now you say you've changed, so I'm gonna trust you.
但如果你犯过的错导致了麻烦
But if those mistakes you made come back to haunt you,
你别指望我帮你遮掩
you will not expect me to cover for you.
现在我们是搭档
Now we may be partners,
甚至是朋友
and we might even be friends,
可是  我仍然是警察
but, um, I'm still a cop.
明白吗
Understood?
听清楚了  一清二楚
Yeah, I hear you. Loud and clear.
我12小时内回家
I'll be home in 12 hours
帮忙下一个号码
to help with the next number.
恐怕那就晚了
I'm afraid that'll be too late.
下一个号码已经来了
The next number's already come up,
只不过不是新号码
only it's not new.
是我们过去帮过的人吗
Someone we've helped before?
是我们正在帮助的人
Someone we're currently helping.
罗根・皮尔斯
Logan Pierce.
他又有了新的威胁
There's another threat against him,
或者有人和那律师合谋害他
or else someone is conspiring with the lawyer.
我所能确信的是
All I know for certain
皮尔斯正处于危险之中
is that Pierce is in immediate danger.
我赶回酒吧去
I'm headed back to the club now.
不需要  我黑进了皮尔斯的信用卡账户
No need. I was able to hack Pierce's credit card account.
他的卡刚刚在
His card was just used
圣彼得堡的维谢拉大酒店刷过了
at the Grand Vishera Hotel in St. Petersburg.
地址发给你了
I'm sending you the address.
酒店就在桥那边
It's right over the bridge.
皮尔斯  是约翰
Pierce, it's John.
站住
Stop right there.
他警告过我  有人会来
He warned me someone would come.
我已经通知了保安  出去
I've called security, get out.
艾米莉  你在干什么
Emily, what are you doing here?
我说了出去  快
I said get out, now!
里瑟先生  怎么回事
Mr. Reese, what's going on?
艾米莉・莫顿
Emily Morton.
金爱网
她活得好好的  而且还挺会
She's alive and appears to be a pretty good...
开枪
shot.
你刚说的什么意思  他警告你有人会来
What do you mean, he warned you someone else would come?
他是指谁
Who's he?
维谢拉大酒店
顾客姓名  罗根・皮尔斯
皮尔斯安排你住在这酒店的  对不对
Pierce put you up at this hotel, didn't he?
芬奇  艾米莉不是在跟皮尔斯作对
Finch, Emily's not working against Pierce.
她在跟他合作
She's working with him.
自从皮尔斯一周前
I haven't seen Pierce since he came
来过我公寓后我就再也没见他了
by my apartment about a week ago.
他说有人要对付我们  让我收拾好行李
Said someone was on to us, told me to pack a bag,
好让我完成金爱网
so I could finish Alchementary.
我们本来打算明天公布这一项目
We planned to announce our project tomorrow.
艾米莉的技术会抢"友网"的生意
Emily's technology will cannibalize Friendczar's business.
看样子与皮尔斯最亲近的人
It seems the person closest to Pierce
将承受最多损失
is the one with the most to lose.
贾斯汀
Justin?
是你吗  伙计
Is that you, buddy?
看样子公司要分裂了
Well, I guess we're breaking up the company.
抱歉  皮尔斯
Sorry, Pierce.
这是你自找的
But you brought this on yourself.
-不不不  -给我们一分钟
- No, no, no! - Give us a minute.
我一直都知道会有女人介入我们之间
Always knew a woman would come between us.
就是想不到
Just didn't think it'd be
你是因为更喜欢她的技术
'cause you liked her technology better.
害我们分裂的不是艾米莉
Emily didn't break us up,
贾斯汀  而是你
Justin, you did.
她甚至让我想起了你
You know, she actually reminds me of you,
以前的你
how you used to be--
有热情  有原则
passionate, principled.
你还没有决心欺负
Before you decided we need to bully
和毁灭所有竞争对手之前
and bury our competition.
我没听到你反对
I didn't hear you objecting.
那是因为你没有好好听
That's 'cause you weren't listening to me.
我告诉过你多少次
How many times did I tell you
我不想用那种方式做生意
I don't wanna run a business like that?
你根本就不想做生意
You didn't wanna run a business at all,
所有的事都是我在做
left me to do everything.
我开始还以为你是失去理智了
I thought maybe you'd gone off the deep end,
才在城里半裸着晃荡
parading around town half-naked,
去科尼岛开董事会议
taking board meetings at Coney Island.
然后我意识到了
Then I realized,
如果董事会开除了你
if the board pushed you out,
你的竞业禁止条款就作废了
your non-compete clause would be null and void,
你就可以发布艾米莉的技术
and you could take Emily's technology public.
艾米莉的创意更好
Emily's idea's better.
那才是人们想要的  能完美匹配
It's what people want, the perfect match
爱情  友情  甚至商业伙伴
in love and friendship, even business.
你懂什么叫友情吗
What do you know about friends?
你所有的朋友都想让你死
All your friends want you dead.
连你新朋友都抛弃你了
Even your new pal's left you.
把他扔下去
Dump him.
不  不
No, no!
不  等等
No! Wait, wait!
等等
Wait!
这正是我设计好的  知道吧
I had 'em right where I wanted 'em, you know?
你得交点新朋友了  皮尔斯
You need to get new friends, Pierce.
严重同意  伙计
I couldn't agree with you more, man.
被动手机麦克风监听
主体: 辅助系统管理员
会话分析
语言识别
现在  要么我们一起继续其他事情
Now either we move on to the next thing together,
要么算了
or we don't.
你决定
You decide.
监测到威胁
主体: 安娜・桑德斯
社保号码: XXX-XX-2406
分类
无关号码
应急预案功能激活
联络辅助系统管理员
安娜・桑德斯
前男友
家暴
攻击
限制令
今天贾斯汀・奥美  "友网"的共同创始人之一
Today Justin Ogilvy, the co-founder of Friendczar.com,
遭到起诉
was brought up on charges
罪名是试图加害其合伙人罗根・皮尔斯
for attempting to murder his partner Logan Pierce
该案案情奇怪
in what can only be described as a bizarre case.
有些友情注定难以持久
Some friendships aren't made to last.
"友网"的首发股价在罗根・皮尔斯宣布
The Friendczar IPO has continued its downward slump
即将开办新公司后持续暴跌
after an announcement that Logan Pierce is launching a new company
新公司与"友网"将产生竞争关系
that's in direct competition with Friendczar.
皮尔斯的合伙人是软件工程师艾米莉・莫顿
Pierce is partnering with software engineer Emily Morton
以及令人意想不到的  皮尔斯的前对手本・卡盟
and surprisingly, Ben Kamin, his former rival.
谢谢你  詹妮特  现在一起来关注天气
Thanks, Janet, now turning our attention to the weather.
好了  橡皮糖  准备受刑吧
All right, chewie, prepare to get posterized.
我听说你老妈一屁股坐在了iPhone上
You know, I heard your mother sat on her iPhone,
直接给压成iPad了  是真的吗  伙计
and it turned to an iPad. Is that true, man?
真的吗
Is it true?
拜托
Come on now.
我可以来一整天
I could go all day.
谁进了下一个球  就可以得到对方的车
Next bucket gets the other guy's car.
或者说你们的自行车
Or in your case, your bike,
或者是交通卡之类的
or Metrocard, whatever.
赌就赌了
Bet's a bet.
作弊  你这是作弊
Whoa, thief! You are a thief.
我们要重新发球的  你们也听到
We said check the ball. You guys hear--
你们也听到我说要重新发球了  对吧
You heard me say check the ball, right?
没有啊  这就是篮球  你自己说的
No, that's ball game, what you said.
我开玩笑的  爱现小子
I'm just kidding, showboat.
我言出必行
I'm a man of my word.
你是疯子
Man, you crazy.
我听说过了
Yeah, I've heard that.
玩得不错
You got some game.
你充满惊喜
You're full of surprises.
-你有脸说这话  -是吗
- You're one to talk. - Yeah?
跟你的竞争对手卡盟合作
Partnering with Kamin, your competition.
那家伙很正直的  知道不
The guy's a straight shooter, you know?
再说  艾米莉的软件说我们俩合拍啊
Plus, Emily's software said we're totally compatible,
虽然跟他老婆不太合
not so much with his wife though.
有件事我不明白
One thing I don't get--
你警告过艾米莉小心奥美
you warned Emily about Ogilvy.
你知道他要对付你
And you knew he was after you.
为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?
你没听说吗
Haven't you heard?
我毫不顾及自己的安危
I have a reckless disregard for my own safety.
你就是想看我是怎么工作的
You just wanted to see how I worked.
我终于明白了
You know, I finally figured it out,
你为什么要做这个
why you do what you do.
利他主义
Altruism.
这样有用吗
How's that working out for you?
略表谢意
Just a little thank-you.
我想你又要去救
So I guess you will be moving on
下一个倒霉的陌生人了吧
to your next hapless stranger?
至少我可以载你一程
I can at least give you a lift.
其实吧
Actually, I, uh--
我还是坐地铁好了
I think I'll take the subway.
我们来这儿干吗  芬奇
What are we doing here, Finch?
又有号码了吗
Do we have another number?
不是  来约会
No, a date.
你为我安排了约会
You got me a date?
不是你  是小熊
Not you. Bear.
他需要朋友
He needs a friend.
你好
Hello.
去吧
Go.
想法不错嘛  芬奇
Good thinking, Finch.
那位亿万富豪给了我点东西
Our billionaire gave me a little something.
精确到纳秒
Tells time to the nanosecond.
这表很贵的
That was a very expensive watch.
还是礼物呢
Not to mention, a gift.
带GPS的礼物
A gift equipped with GPS.
一个拥有无限资源的狡猾亿万富豪
A cunning billionaire with unlimited resources.
这位朋友的好奇心可真危险
Our friend is just curious enough to be dangerous.
威胁到系统管理员
GPS发射器
追踪信号
信号无法追踪
接收者未知
监控主体
罗根・皮尔斯